Good morning, Night City! Rise and shine
for a new day in the City of Dreams…
Got reports of a pile-up
on the Heywood highway.
We've got gonks dreaming of
becoming the next Weyland Boa Boa
jamming up traffic for the rest of us!
…gangoons swarming like flies! What is it
about this City that keeps attracting…
Never fear the risk!
You'll never make it big
dreaming quiet, dreaming small.
Wanna know where
all the legends of Night City play?
It's…
Maine.
When's the last time you ate?
You're shaking. All that chrome's
messing with your nerves.
When this's over, you gotta refit.
Go lightspec, reduce your load.
Just some jitters.
Don't make it a big deal.
Shit, at this rate…
A lil' metal ain't gonna…
Maine?
Hey! Maine!
Fuck off!
No one's gonna set my limits but me!
I made it this far without any trouble.
I ain't gonna turn back now!
Where's the fucking data?!
You know Kiwi's diving for it!
ICE is thicker than I expected…
Maine! Stop! What're you…
Hey!
Kiwi? Falco?
You back with us? Shit…
Dorio?
What gives? We get jumped?
What happened to Kiwi…
…forecast for heavy rainfall on the coast.
Districts like Santo Domingo
and Westbrook,
are bound to see showers
from midnight to sunrise--
What the fuck, Falco?!
Ask Maine? Just tell me…
Yo!
Huh…?
I won't do it.
How'd Kiwi land on an op table?
She was on Tanaka's case, right?
What went wrong?
Ask the gonk next to me.
Fuck off.
Maine punched her out. Lost his cool when
she ran into some ICE that snagged her…
What!?
Maine. How about you
get your head checked?
Maine, next time you start losing it--
Hey…
"Losing it"…?
Cyberpsychosis.
Maine!
Uh… Hey.
Dorio just told me. You…
You'll be fine, right?
You won't end up like…
Fine?
What you mean by "fine"? Kid.
You asking if I'm going psycho?
You think I'm losing it?
Maine, I didn't say…
Lay off, kid.
Your snooping around's
getting on my nerves.
You think you're hot shit
'cause you're faster than me?
That Sandy was supposed to be mine.
I made it this far.
Ain't no way I'm gonna downgrade now…
Can't stop running now…
The pigs probably have our trail already.
We only got 'til morning, if that.
Are you hearing me?
I said no!
You're the one that's not listening!
He's Arasaka…
Let's call it off.
C'mon, Lucy.
You don't gotta do it.
Shut it, David!
We can drop Tanaka where we took him.
Pretend none of this happened.
You've got a lot of nerve!
I'm not done with you!
David… Tell me I can do it.
Wha… I thought…
Tell me!
You don't understand
what Arasaka's like at all.
They're always watching us. You… me…
We can't just call it off.
We don't have a choice.
I know that.
But… I need you to tell me that I can.
Please…
I'm sorry, Lucy. I…
I know you can do this.
I believe in you, Lucy.
I'll do it.
What?
But David's coming, too.
And kick Maine out.
Those are my conditions.
Fine.
But you'll keep us in the loop.
Pings every quarter hour.
You've got until daybreak.
Don't screw this up!
David! Where's Maine?
Hell if I know!
Maine!
Dorio…
Hey, you sure we don't need
Dorio for backup?
Grow a spine.
Why didn't you…
You should've told me.
Why's it gotta be just the two of us?
David.
H-Hey…
Why were you hiding your deep-dive port?
Jacking in now…
David…
Yeah?
I'm going in.
Where there's a trap,
there has to be an entryway.
We gonna kill him?
We need a plan
in case she doesn't make it.
Wouldn't have needed one
if you weren't feeling like shit.
You're willing to bet everything
on a backup runner?
Absolutely.
Tick tock, Maine.
Arasaka is still short one executive.
I trust you understand
there's no room for error.
Made that clear.
What?!
The fuck you staring at, Faraday?
A glitch…?
Damn it… Now of all times!
W-Wait…
Wait, please!
David!
Maine! Snap out of it!
Hey!
Damn it! Why is he waking up?!
What are you doing, David?!
I knew it… You're David…
How do you…
I've heard much about you.
Your incident with my son at the Academy…
And despite that, I ordered
your readmittance to the Academy.
You?
Please, David. You can stop this.
I don't want to die.
We just need the data. You won't…
Don't be so naive!
I've seen their faces!
Do you believe Arasaka
won't hunt them down?
Listen to me.
Why do you think I lifted your expulsion?
You have exceptional abilities.
I believe you could become
a valuable asset to Arasaka!
We could give you a great future, David!
Do not throw your life to waste!
This is it.
I can't let you go.
Then get in contact with Arasaka.
It will all be over
in less than five minutes.
That ain't what I mean!
I can't betray my crew.
Stupid boy.
Don't you see you're being used?
And Arasaka won't?
No. You are blind.
Who do you think is paying for this stunt?
It has Militech written all over it.
All roads lead back to the corporations.
Regardless of
how high you climb in this world,
you will never amount to the lowest corpo.
That's not…
David?
David… What…
What is it that you want?
What do I want…?
David! What the fuck?!
He's awake!
Where's his tranq… Hand it over!
Fuck! What just happened?!
Shit! It's all over if he flatlines!
David!
Snap out of it, David!
You got her in, right?!
Now get her out!
Dorio! Lucy's still stuck in deep-dive!
-What?!
-Hurry! Disconnect her!
Alright! Pull her out!
The data?
Jabbed him right after
his heart stopped… so probably good.
David!
Yeah, Lucy's--
David! What the fuck were you doing?
What about you?
What the fuck were you doing?
What did you say?
Knocking Kiwi out…
Dropping all this on Lucy's lap.
What the fuck's been up with you?!
Kid, don't start…
Maine! David!
Jammer got fried when Tanaka flatlined!
Trauma Team caught the signal!
Motherfuck!
David, we ain't done yet!
But prep our wheels, quick!
Get it together, David!
You volunteered for this, so do it!
Wait in the ride. We'll catch up.
I know!
Fucking Platinum premium plan service…
Dorio!
Registering gunfire in the service area.
Possible hostiles present.
Requesting NCPD backup in force.
David?
Lucy! You alright?
What's going on?
Tanaka woke up, but his brain
suddenly fried for some reason.
Did something happen in there?
Where's Maine and Dorio?
They're bringing Tanaka's body…
But he's dead.
We saved him.
Why?!
What do you mean? We still need the data.
There's no point bringing him.
There was no data.
No way…
Fuck. We're definitely on
'Saka's radar now.
Maine! Don't forget to take your meds!
Just took a shot!
Don't move!
Fuck! Why's NCPD always fast
when it comes to us?
Back up! Go to the back!
Fuck! They won't pick up!
David!
Where are you going?
Gonna go help.
No! What if they slip out another way?
We're waiting!
I'm going.
David!
What are you so afraid of?!
It shouldn't be taking 'em this long!
Wait!
I got a signal. Trauma is here…
alongside the NCPD.
They're surrounded.
Then we gotta help.
No! Do you want to die?!
I won't die. I'll come back to you.
David…
They might not make it.
We should cut our losses and run.
We can still hear them fighting!
They're still alive!
You're acting weird today, Lucy.
You saw something, didn't you?
In Tanaka's neural net…
I… only wanted to…
Lucy?
Aren't you gonna tell me
that you believe in me, too?
The fuck, Maine?!
Get it together…
Shit! Fucking gonk…
Don't shoot!
Why not?!
He's holding a platinum client hostage!
Not our problem!
Dorio…
Maine… Hold on, I'm on my way.
I need…
I need you to tell me I can do this.
Was this…
Was this my fault?
Freeze! Weapons down,
hands behind your head!
Last warning!
Platinum client confirmed dead.
Hey.
Is this my fault?
It's cyberpsychosis!
Flag MaxTac now…
Got a cyberpsy--
Client has flatlined. Evacuate!
Hey, where are you going?!
Client policy's void!
This's your problem now!
Fuck that!
He's here! Get us out!
Shit!
David… Can you hear me?
Maine's gone psycho.
They've called in MaxTac.
Turn around, come back…
Maine…
Oh. Hey, kid.
You alright?
Maine, I came to back you up…
Uh…
Dorio's dead.
What?
What are you doing…?
Last thing I can do for her.
Let's run, Maine.
You're gonna die.
No more running. Reaper's calling my name.
What are you saying?
Fine. I'll fight too.
Kid…
I've already made up my mind.
I'll do it! I'll save you.
Damn it! Stop shaking!
Fuck you, MaxTac! Come and get us!
Maine, we can get through this together.
We'll get through this. And then… then…
David.
You can't do it.
Why… Maine…
Why…
David.
This is the end of the line for me.
But not for you.
Fast is what you do, remember?
Keep running.